<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- There must be a date and editor attribute for the weeklyEmail.
	 There also must be a teaser and an itemList which are children of the weeklyEmail.
	 Every item must have a name and category.
	 type attribute for item can be "new", "urgent" or omitted.
	 deadline attribute is for reference only.
	 date and location children of the item are optional, but info is required.
	 Items will be displayed in the order they appear, grouped by category based on the order of the categories.-->
<weeklyEmail date="September 5, 2013" volume="0" issue="0" editor="Evan Ott">
	<teaser>Official email from the UT Austin Chapter of the Society of Physics Students</teaser>
	<itemList>
		<item name="Intro to SPS" category="Weekly Meetings" type="urgent" deadline="September 5th">
			<date>September 5th, 6pm</date>
			<location>RLM 11.204</location>
			<info>Come hear what UT SPS is all about! We'll be talking about what different activities we're planning and would love for the meeting to be as interactive as possible! Unfortunately, we won't have pizza this week but we will next week!</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Physics Careers" category="Weekly Meetings" type="new" deadline="September 12th">
			<date>September 12th, 6pm</date>
			<location>CPE 2.208</location>
			<info>Dr. Franks from the Career Design Center will join us to talk about careers in physics and what resources are available on campus for finding jobs! We'll also unveil a project we'll be working on with the Career Design Center over the course of the semester. If time permits, SPS President, Evan Ott, will present his research from this summer at Sandia National Laboratories.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Physnic" category="Social Events" type="urgent" deadline="September 6th">
			<date>September 6th, 5pm</date>
			<location>Eastwoods Park</location>
			<info>This Friday is the Physnic (Physics Department Picnic)! Come to Eastwoods Park just Northeast of RLM at 5pm and get some delicious BBQ! You might even play some Ultimate Frisbee with your professors! It's a great time for the Department of Physics and a great way to meet your fellow physicists!</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Comments or Questions" category="Contact Us" deadline="Never">
			<info>Have something to complain about? Or a question? Maybe an idea for a meeting or event? Or suggestions about how we use technology? Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:spsofficers@gmail.com"&gt;spsofficers@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or see the links below!</info>
		</item>
	</itemList>
</weeklyEmail>
