<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- There must be a date and editor attribute for the weeklyEmail.
	 There also must be a teaser and an itemList which are children of the weeklyEmail.
	 Every item must have a name and category.
	 type attribute for item can be "new", "urgent" or omitted.
	 deadline attribute is for reference only.
	 date and location children of the item are optional, but info is required.
	 Items will be displayed in the order they appear, grouped by category based on the order of the categories.-->
<weeklyEmail date="September 5, 2013" volume="0" issue="0" editor="Evan Ott">
	<teaser>Official email from the UT Austin Chapter of the Society of Physics Students</teaser>
	<itemList>
		<item name="Physics Careers" category="Weekly Meetings" deadline="September 12th">
			<date>September 12th, 6pm</date>
			<location>CPE 2.208</location>
			<info>Dr. Franks from the Career Design Center will join us to talk about careers in physics and what resources are available on campus for finding jobs! We'll also unveil a project we'll be working on with the Career Design Center over the course of the semester. If time permits, SPS President, Evan Ott, will present his research from this summer at Sandia National Laboratories.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Dr. Willy Fischler" category="Weekly Meetings" type="new" deadline="September 19th">
			<date>September 19, 6pm</date>
			<location>CPE 2.208</location>
			<info>Join SPS as we welcome UT Physics professor Dr. Willy Fischler! He will be talking about research, life, and more! His reseach interests include: "quantum field theory, supersymmetry, string theory, quantum cosmology, and statistical mechanics" &lt;a href="http://zippy.ph.utexas.edu/~fischler/"&gt;his website&lt;/a&gt;</info>
		</item>
		<item name="SPS Intro Presentation" category="Weekly Meetings" deadline="Never">
			<info>Miss the first SPS meeting and want to know more about us? You can download a PDF of the presentation &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/2013/09/SPS_Intro.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and if you really want to know more, take a look at our 2012-2013 Chapter Report we submitted to the National SPS organization to try to win an "Outstanding Chapter" award (no announcements yet on that front!), which can be found &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/UofTexasatAustin-2013SPSChapterReport.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Sense Corp Hiring" category="Careers" type="urgent" deadline="September 11th">
			<date>September 11, 3pm-5pm</date>
			<location>Rec Sports Center</location>
			<info>Dr. Franks from the Career Design Center passed on some information about a mid-sized consulting firm that is interested in hiring students with a strong background in mathematics after being extremely impressed with two math
			students last year. They will be at the McCombs (business school) Undergraduate Career Expo on the 11th. Attire requirements are
			&lt;a href="http://www.mccombs.utexas.edu/~/media/Files/MSB/BBA/CS/08%20-%20F13%20-%20Instructional%20Guide%20-%20Business%20Attire.ashx"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; and list of all employers attending is
			&lt;a href="https://msb-utexas-csm.symplicity.com/events/students.php?mode=list&cf=utbbafall2013"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt. Finally, here is a brief summary of Sense Corp:
			&lt;p&gt;Sense Corp is a fast-growing team of exceptionally talented consultants. Our people are the best and brightest talent from leading firms and universities. The founder and many employees
			of Sense Corp are UT graduates, and we value UT's campus to provide quality consultants for our company. Our firm is committed to making a difference by working together with our clients on
			multi-level business challenges. Our strength comes from the people we hire; and we, therefore strongly support each individual's professional development. You will quickly learn to become a
			leader as you gain increasing responsibilities to help our clients in a broad spectrum of industries.&lt;p&gt;Information about job postings for Sense Corp can be found on our website
			&lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/2013/09/Sense%20Corp%20Job%20Descriptions.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and you can direct any and all questions to
			&lt;a href="mailto:ruth.franks@austin.utexas.edu"&gt;ruth.franks@austin.utexas.edu&lt;/a&gt;.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Career Design Center" category="Careers" type="new" deadline="Never">
			<info>The College of Natural Sciences' Career Design Center is hosting several events this semester for career prep and other interesting events. &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/2013/09/CDC%20%Fall%20Events.pdf"&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; is a handy list of some of those events, which includes the CNS Career Expo on the 16th (see below).</info>
		</item>

		<item name="Comments or Questions" category="Contact Us" deadline="Never">
			<info>Have something to complain about? Or a question? Maybe an idea for a meeting or event? Or suggestions about how we use technology? Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:spsofficers@gmail.com"&gt;spsofficers@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or see the links below! As always, Don't Forget To Be Awesome!</info>
		</item>
	</itemList>
</weeklyEmail>
