<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- There must be a date and editor attribute for the weeklyEmail.
	 There also must be a teaser and an itemList which are children of the weeklyEmail.
	 Every item must have a name and category.
	 type attribute for item can be "new", "urgent" or omitted.
	 deadline attribute is for reference only.
	 date and location children of the item are optional, but info is required.
	 Items will be displayed in the order they appear, grouped by category based on the order of the categories.-->
<weeklyEmail date="September 15, 2013">
	<teaser>Official email from the UT Austin Chapter of the Society of Physics Students</teaser>
	<itemList>
		<!-- SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENTS -->
		<!-- item name="PHY 302K LA Position" category="Special Announcement" type="urgent" deadline="September 13th" -->
		<!-- WEEKLY MEETINGS --
		<item name="Dr. Willy Fischler" category="Weekly Meetings" deadline="September 19th">
			<date>September 19, 6pm</date>
			<location>CPE 2.208</location>
			<info>Join SPS as we welcome UT Physics professor Dr. Willy Fischler! He will be talking about research, life, and more! His reseach interests include: "quantum field theory, supersymmetry, string theory, quantum cosmology, and statistical mechanics."</info>
		</item>
		<item name="SPS Intro Presentation" category="Weekly Meetings" deadline="Never">
			<info>Miss the first SPS meeting and want to know more about us? You can download a PDF of the presentation &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/2013/09/SPS_Intro.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, and if you really want to know more, take a look at our 2012-2013 Chapter Report we submitted to the National SPS organization to try to win an "Outstanding Chapter" award (no announcements yet on that front!), which can be found &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/UofTexasatAustin-2013SPSChapterReport.pdf"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Physics Careers" category="Weekly Meetings" deadline="Never">
			<info>Check out &lt;a href="www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/2013/09/Careers.pptx"&gt;this presentation&lt;/a&gt; from Dr. Franks in the Career
		Design Center for some quick tips about the CNS Career Expo TOMORROW (Monday)! Plus
		some general career-related resources for you in the college.</info>
		</item>

		<!-- SPS ACTIVITIES -->
		<item name="Mentoring Groups" category="SPS Activities" type="new" deadline="Never">
			<info>Interested in being in one of the mentoring groups but didn't sign up at one of the weekly meetings?
			You can sign up &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1QKbh6-eG48vqghmArxMmzSZAg1eUuy38IUIVaCRx1TE/viewform"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to be a mentee and 
			&lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1GNN-e1Ep0HJa3LEYPoNlsS72UVJeqMOQGT5n_T3H1v8/viewform"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; to be a mentor. Email
			Tharon Morrison at &lt;a href="mailto:t_morrison@utexas.edu"&gt;t_morrison@utexas.edu&lt;/a&gt; for more information.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="SPS Potluck!" category="SPS Activities" type="new" deadline="September 20th">
			<date>September 20, 6pm?</date>
			<info>Next Friday we'll have our first SPS potluck of the year, hosted at Evan and Tharon's apartment. Please sign up to bring food &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AiDFKF73inhGdHNYX3BPSGhCUmp1b241Uk9GOGYtaUE&usp=sharing"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. If you're on campus,
feel free to bring "easier" food like chips/soda if you don't have easy access to a kitchen. The apartment complex (info in the Google Spreadsheet above) has a pool, so feel free to bring swim gear! Questions should go to Evan Ott at &lt;a href="mailto:evan.ott@utexas.edu"&gt;evan.ott@utexas.edu&lt;/a&gt;</</info>
		</item>
		<item name="League of Legends Tournament/LAN Party" category="SPS Activities" type="new" deadline="Never">
			<info>Do you play LoL (League of Legends)? Want to play with some of your fellow physicists? SPS is hoping to host a LAN party / tournament of sorts in the near future. If you're interested, you can sign up &lt;a href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1fhS3RH8sUHS96u5cjr7xPhYmHUQ2KB_VIOdMwXBWeu0/viewform"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt; or
email SPS webmaster, Tharon Morrison at &lt;a href="mailto:t_morrison@utexas.edu"&gt;t_morrison@utexas.edu&lt;/a&gt;</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Sunday Night Study Session" category="SPS Activities" deadline="Never">
			<date>Sundays, 6pm-???</date>
			<location>RLM 7.116</location>
			<info>It's back! Our Sunday Night Study Session (SNSS) is in full swing! For those who haven't been, every week we invite any and all physics majors and people in physics or math classes to come by to work on homework.
			With many upper-division students in attendance (and some LAs for classes), when you run into problems, you won't be stuck for long. We also provide cookies, coffee, tea, etc., to help keep you &lt;s&gt;caffeinated&lt;/s&gt;
			energized. Some come by to help or be helped! If you're interested in tutoring, making known that you're available during the night (name on a chalkboard) is a great way to earn service hours for
			Sigma Pi Sigma.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Sigma Pi Sigma Service Hours" category="SPS Activities" deadline="Never">
			<info>Interested in joining Sigma Pi Sigma, the physics honors society? The requirements are listed on &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/pages/EPE.html"&gt;our website&lt;/a&gt;. For the service hour component,
			we will be managing that through the new HornsLink system (see below for the link). Join the SPS group and when you volunteer (like tutoring for SNSS above), submit a request for us to verify your service hours. That way,
			we have a nice record of volunteers and volunteer time (and it will show up on the resume HornsLink can create for you)! You input the time you worked, we sign off, then you don't have to think about it again!</info>
		</item>

		<!-- CAREERS -->
		<item name="Career Design Center" category="Careers" deadline="Never">
			<info>The College of Natural Sciences' Career Design Center is hosting several events this semester for career prep and other interesting events. &lt;a href="http://www.ph.utexas.edu/~sps/resources/2013/09/CDC%20%Fall%20Events.pdf"&gt;This&lt;/a&gt; is a handy list of some of those events, which includes the CNS Career Expo on the 16th (see below).</info>
		</item>
		<item name="CNS Career Expo" category="Careers" type="urgent" deadline="September 16th">
			<date>September 16th, 1pm-6pm</date>
			<location>Frank Erwin Center</location>
			<info>The semesterly Career Expo is already almost upon us! Looking for an internship? Or
			maybe a full-time position starting in the summer (yes, that far in advance)? Then go to the
			Career Expo!!! By my count (and by that I mean Adobe's), there are at least 25 companies
			interested in hiring physics majors, including places as diverse as: Applied Research
			Laboratories (ARL) here in Austin, athenahealth, Bloomberg, Intel, Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL),
			National Instruments, and Sandia National Laboratories. And many companies that don't have
			"Physics" listed as a desired major may be willing to bend the rules if you have programming
			experience or can convince them that you are very good at solving problems (a big part of
			physics).&lt;p&gt;
			Information on expected attire and a list of companies (and some tips) can be found on the
			Career Design Center's website &lt;a href="http://cns.utexas.edu/career-design-center/career-events"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. If you have questions,
			you can contact them (info on website), or ask a fellow physicist!</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Job Openings" category="Careers" type="new" deadline="Never">
			<info>The SPS officers get several emails each week about positions in various companies / organizations, and we want to pass them along but don't want to further increase the length of these messages. Therefore,
			we'll be updating our website in the coming week or two to link to information then reference it in these emails. At the moment, we have some info about a summer internship in the Petroleum and Geosystems Engineering department, positions for this semester at the non-profit Undergraduate Computational Finance, and consulting organization iRunway. If you'd like the info we have on any of these, please email us. Otherwise, we'll be posting things as they come in.</info>
		</item>
		<!-- CONTACT US -->
		<item name="Comments or Questions" category="Contact Us" deadline="Never">
			<info>Have something to complain about? Or a question? Maybe an idea for a meeting or event? Or suggestions about how we use technology? Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:spsofficers@gmail.com"&gt;spsofficers@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or see the links below! As always, Don't Forget To Be Awesome!</info>
		</item>
	</itemList>
</weeklyEmail>
