<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- There must be a date and editor attribute for the weeklyEmail.
	 There also must be a teaser and an itemList which are children of the weeklyEmail.
	 Every item must have a name and category.
	 type attribute for item can be "new", "urgent", "updated" or omitted.
	 deadline attribute is for reference only.
	 date and location children of the item are optional, but info is required.
	 Items will be displayed in the order they appear, grouped by category based on the order of the categories.-->
<weeklyEmail date="February 2, 2014">
	<teaser>Official email from the UT Austin Chapter of the Society of Physics Students</teaser>
	<itemList>
		<item name="February 2, 2014" category="Message from the President">
			<info>
				Very exciting times for SPS! We have a guest speaker, Jill Tietjen, coming
				to speak in a couple weeks, a potluck coming up on 2/15, and a new undergraduate
				lecture series starting Tuesday! I encourage you to read about all of this (and more!) below. During our meeting tomorrow, we'll talk about the big physics news
				of the week: Magnetic Monopoles (well, synthetic ones anyway).
				&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;~Evan Ott, SPS President
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENTS -->
		<item name="Guest Speaker Jill Tietjen" category="Special Announcements" type="new">
			<date>February 17, 6:30pm</date>
			<location>WEL 1.308</location>
			<info>
				Former national president of the Society of Women in Engineers, Jill Tietjen,
				will be on campus in two weeks to talk about "Discovering Scientific, Technical,
				Engineering, and Mathematical Women: The accomplishments of pioneering women
				engineers, scientists, and inventors over the course of U.S. History." uWip,
				GirlAdvocates!, and SPS are partnering to sponsor this event in the place of the
				usual SPS meeting. For more, see the
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/573730322712213/"&gt;
				Facebook event&lt;/a&gt;.
				&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/573730322712213/"&gt; &lt;img width="450px" align="center" src="https://scontent-a-atl.xx.fbcdn.net/hphotos-prn1/t1/1510811_659474367442368_382733384_n.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- WEEKLY MEETINGS -->
		<item name="Small Learning Communities" category="Weekly Meetings" type="new">
			<date>February 3, 6:30pm</date>
			<location>RLM 7.104</location>
			<info>
				This week, we'll have senior physics major Amanda Turbyfill leading a discussion
				on small learning communities. Amanda is part of the College Tuition and Budget
				Advisory Committee for CNS, which is working on how to better address issues that affect
				our community such as: having small learning groups, increasing representation
				of minorities and women in science, and finding better ways to integrate technology
				in the classroom. The CNS Town Hall on Wednesday (see below) is part of this
				same initiative, and there is more info on their efforts
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/644236828950937/"
				&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. See you there!
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Undergrad Research Presentation: Luke Pharr" category="Weekly Meetings" type="new">
			<date>February 10, 6:30pm</date>
			<location>RLM 7.104</location>
			<info>
				Luke Pharr is a third-year physics and Plan II major. He grew up in Austin
				where he fostered a love for science. Luke currently researches
				buckling of thin polyethylene sheets in the Center for Nonlinear Dynamics
				here at UT Physics.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!--CNS Activities -->
		<item name="Town Hall: The Freshman Experience" category="CNS Activities" type="new">
			<date>February 5, 5pm</date>
			<location>WCH 1.120</location>
			<info>
				CNS has many resources for freshmen, but it wants to hear about how effective
				they are - anything from FIGs to the FRI, from Residence Hall Study Groups
				to academic advisors. Come for some free pizza (and prizes!) and come help
				shape new (and old) initiatives to make our college the best it can be (and
				make sure us physicists are represented!)! More info is already in your inbox
				from Dr. Kopp (subject: "Week of 2/3/14 -- Remember freshman year? We want to
				talk to you!").
				&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/644236828950937/"&gt; &lt;img width="450px" align="center" src="https://fbcdn-sphotos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-prn2/t1/1546024_10203011706199750_1080101138_n.jpg"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			</info>
		</item>

		<!-- SPS Activities -->
		<item name="Undergraduate Lecture Series" category="SPS Activities" type="updated">
			<date>Tuesdays, 5pm</date>
			<location>CLA 0.128</location>
			<info>Senior Eric Horsley has put together a student lecture series where
			 each week an undergraduate will present a physics topic he or she
			 finds interesting. Many talks are already scheduled, with the first
			 being Eric's &lt;b&gt;this&lt;/b&gt; Tuesday (2/4): "In Search of Phase Space in Quantum Mechanics." Come
			 learn some physics! For more information, contact Eric at
			 &lt;a href="mailto:ehorsley171619@gmail.com"&gt;ehorsley171619@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Cooking with Physicists" category="SPS Activities" type="updated">
			<date>February 15, 5pm</date>
			<location>Evan and Tharon's Apartment</location>
			<info>
				Our first social event of the semester will be a potluck/cookout of sorts
				at the apartment of the president and vice-president! We'll have cooking
				appliances set up to have everyone bring some ingredients to make something
				delicious! Help coordinate ingredients on the Facebook event
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/216720731850037/"
				&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;! Or you can tell us what you'd like to bring
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AkIgZqZWzKKYdDFSNFVTSFM5RkRIU3RPaUQ3RFAtY3c"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Prospective Students Day" category="SPS Activities" type="updated">
			<info>&lt;b&gt;We still need space for 30+ students!&lt;/b&gt; Prospective Students Day is coming up March 21-22 (new date!) and we need dorm
				floors for prospective students to sleep on. If you are willing to
				let someone sleep on your floor please fill out this
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/14D4SRERMfWi5RwQc2pV5upxhxTqa5vScf5EJCdOuQj0/viewform"&gt;form&lt;/a&gt;. 
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Sunday Night Study Session" category="SPS Activities">
			<date>Sundays, 6pm-???</date>
			<location>RLM 7.116</location>
			<info>It's back! Our Sunday Night Study Session (SNSS) is in full swing! For
				those who haven't been, every week we invite any and all physics majors
				and people in physics or math classes to come by to work on homework.
			With many upper-division students in attendance (and some LAs for classes),
			when you run into problems, you won't be stuck for long. We also provide
			cookies, coffee, tea, etc., to help keep you &lt;s&gt;caffeinated&lt;/s&gt;
			energized. Some come by to help or be helped! If you're interested in
			tutoring, making known that you're available during the night
			(name on a chalkboard) is a great way to earn service hours for
			Sigma Pi Sigma.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Physics Idol (Undergrad Research Competition)" category="SPS Activities">
			<info>
				Don't forget to reserve your slot in the new Undergraduate Research
				Presentation Competition during meetings this semester! Winners will
				be judged by a combination of
				a panel and popular vote, on factors covering aspects of both the
				research itself and its presentation. Prizes will include a custom
				t-shirt and a selection of prizes, not to mention bragging rights and a nice
				bullet-point on the resume! Sign up
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/a/utexas.edu/forms/d/1mtD9AHASiby4K6akdjiJTJSCxl9NJMY3hGkCyrk1RKM/viewform"&gt;
				here&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- Mentoring -->	
		<item name=" Machine Shop, Electronics" category="Mentoring" type="updated">
			<info>Mentoring is taking on a new spin this semester. There are going to be
				streams that encompass our successful workshops and add some new ones.
				We are going to have the Machine Shop Workshop to build skills in making
				experimental apparatuses, and an Electronics Workshop to build
				skills in soldering and circuit design.
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1r0Qd3IriVj5Mb2dTg67TnY4BqqEfeTBWFBdhJlvovxg/viewform"&gt;Sign up
				&lt;/a&gt; if you are interested in participating. If you would like to
				help run one of the streams (especially the journal club) you can sign-up
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1JnesePhZ0jWzcvyeSDXGlpam5DNkSuUDvjtGxceN_jg/viewform"&gt;here
				&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- Physics Orgs -->	
		<item name="Undergraduate Women in Physics" category="Physics Orgs">
			<info>
				UT Undergraduate Women in Physics is founded on the principle of
				promoting equality in the sciences, especially physics, both at UT and
				in the general community. We welcome all people interested in furthering
				that goal! Join their
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://utlists.utexas.edu/sympa/info/uwip"&gt;UTList&lt;/a&gt;
				or &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/200619160136575/"&gt;Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- CAREERS -->
		<!-- CONTACT US -->
		<item name="Comments or Questions" category="Contact Us" deadline="Never">
			<info>Have something to complain about? Or a question? Maybe an idea for a meeting or event? Or suggestions about how we use technology? Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:spsofficers@gmail.com"&gt;spsofficers@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or see the links below! As always, Don't Forget To Be Awesome!</info>
		</item>
	</itemList>
</weeklyEmail>
