<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- There must be a date and editor attribute for the weeklyEmail.
	 There also must be a teaser and an itemList which are children of the weeklyEmail.
	 Every item must have a name and category.
	 type attribute for item can be "new", "urgent", "updated" or omitted.
	 deadline attribute is for reference only.
	 date and location children of the item are optional, but info is required.
	 Items will be displayed in the order they appear, grouped by category based on the order of the categories.-->
<weeklyEmail date="January 25, 2014">
	<teaser>Official email from the UT Austin Chapter of the Society of Physics Students</teaser>
	<itemList>
		
		<!-- SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENTS -->
		<item name="Message from the President" category="Special Announcements" type="new">
			<info>
				Welcome back! We missed you! Hope your semester has gotten off to a great start,
				but isn't there something missing in your life? You feel it too? Oh, that's
				right! It's SPS! We'll, we're back and ready to go! Our first meeting is Monday
				and we already have several events lined up! I encourage you to take a look
				at the events below (or the summary in the sidebar) to find some things you'd
				like to participate in. If you have questions, feel free to reach out to us!
				Hope to see you on Monday (and for some of you, see you in class on Thursday)!
				&lt;br&gt;~Evan Ott, SPS President
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Prospective Students Day" category="Special Announcements" type="new">
			<info>Prospective Students Day is coming up March 21-22 (new date!) and we need dorm
				floors for prospective students to sleep on. If you are willing to
				let someone sleep on your floor please fill out this
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/14D4SRERMfWi5RwQc2pV5upxhxTqa5vScf5EJCdOuQj0/viewform"&gt;form&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Undergraduate Lecture Series" category="Special Announcements" type="new">
			<date>Tuesdays, 5pm</date>
			<location>TBA</location>
			<info>Senior Eric Horsley has put together a student lecture series where
			 each week an undergraduate will present a physics topic he or she
			 finds interesting. Many talks are already scheduled, with the first
			 being Eric's this Tuesday: "In Search of Phase Space in Quantum Mechanics." Come
			 learn some physics! For more information, contact Eric at
			 &lt;a href="mailto:ehorsley171619@gmail.com"&gt;ehorsley171619@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- WEEKLY MEETINGS -->
		<item name="First Meeting" category="Weekly Meetings" type="new">
			<date>January 27, 6:30pm</date>
			<location>RLM 7.104</location>
			<info>Come learn about our plans for the semester, enjoy some 
				pizza and some liquid nitrogen ice cream!</info>
		</item>
		<!--CNS Activities -->
		<!-- Mentoring -->	
		<item name="Journal Club, Machine Shop, Electronics" category="Mentoring" type="new">
			<info>Mentoring is taking on a new spin this semester. There are going to be
				streams that encompass our successful workshops and add some new ones.
				We are going to have a Journal Club to introduce each other to different
				physics topics, the Machine Shop Workshop to build skills in making
				experimental apparatuses, and an Electronics Workshop to build
				skills in soldering and circuit design.
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1r0Qd3IriVj5Mb2dTg67TnY4BqqEfeTBWFBdhJlvovxg/viewform"&gt;Sign up
				&lt;/a&gt; if you are interested in participating. If you would like to
				help run one of the streams (especially the journal club) you can sign-up
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1JnesePhZ0jWzcvyeSDXGlpam5DNkSuUDvjtGxceN_jg/viewform"&gt;here
				&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>

		<!-- SPS Activities -->
		<item name="Sunday Night Study Session" category="SPS Activities">
			<date>Sundays, 6pm-???</date>
			<location>RLM 7.116</location>
			<info>It's back! Our Sunday Night Study Session (SNSS) is in full swing! For
				those who haven't been, every week we invite any and all physics majors
				and people in physics or math classes to come by to work on homework.
			With many upper-division students in attendance (and some LAs for classes),
			when you run into problems, you won't be stuck for long. We also provide
			cookies, coffee, tea, etc., to help keep you &lt;s&gt;caffeinated&lt;/s&gt;
			energized. Some come by to help or be helped! If you're interested in
			tutoring, making known that you're available during the night
			(name on a chalkboard) is a great way to earn service hours for
			Sigma Pi Sigma.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Physics Idol (Undergrad Research Competition)" category="SPS Activities" type="new">
			<info>
				Don't forget to reserve your slot in the new Undergraduate Research
				Presentation Competition during meetings this semester! Winners will
				be judged by a combination of
				a panel and popular vote, on factors covering aspects of both the
				research itself and its presentation. Prizes will include a custom
				t-shirt and a selection of prizes, not to mention bragging rights and a nice
				bullet-point on the resume! Sign up
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/a/utexas.edu/forms/d/1mtD9AHASiby4K6akdjiJTJSCxl9NJMY3hGkCyrk1RKM/viewform"&gt;
				here&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Cooking with Physicists" category="SPS Activities" type="new">
			<date>February 15, 5pm</date>
			<location>Evan and Tharon's Apartment</location>
			<info>
				Our first social event of the semester will be a potluck/cookout of sorts
				at the apartment of the president and vice-president! We'll have cooking
				appliances set up to have everyone bring some ingredients to make something
				delicious! Help coordinate ingredients on the Facebook event
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/events/216720731850037/"
				&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;! More info to come!
			</info>
		</item>
		<item name="T-shirt Distribution" category="SPS Activities" type="new">
			<location>RLM Lobby</location>
			<date>This week!</date>
			<info>We are still distributing t-shirts and polos from last semester.
				We could really use your help to staff the booth on the fourth floor.
				Please sign-up &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/spreadsheet/ccc?key=0AkIgZqZWzKKYdGNjMU9UTXZoSEdFWHR2RmFaanhGZGc"&gt;here
				&lt;/a&gt; when you are available.
			</info>
		</item>
		
		<item name="Valentines' Day Cards" category="SPS Activities" type="new">
			<info>We're bringing back physics Valentines' cards this semester! Look
				for us to pick up a special gift for that special someone or maybe ensnare
				that secret crush of yours with the likeness of Tesla or Feynman and some
				physics-related jokes.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- Physics Orgs -->	
		<item name="Undergraduate Women in Physics" category="Physics Orgs" type="new">
			<info>
				UT Undergraduate Women in Physics is founded on the principle of
				promoting equality in the sciences, especially physics, both at UT and
				in the general community. We welcome all people interested in furthering
				that goal! Join their
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://utlists.utexas.edu/sympa/info/uwip"&gt;UTList&lt;/a&gt;
				or &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/432796033504388/"&gt;Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;.

			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- CAREERS -->
		<!-- CONTACT US -->
		<item name="Comments or Questions" category="Contact Us" deadline="Never">
			<info>Have something to complain about? Or a question? Maybe an idea for a meeting or event? Or suggestions about how we use technology? Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:spsofficers@gmail.com"&gt;spsofficers@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or see the links below! As always, Don't Forget To Be Awesome!</info>
		</item>
	</itemList>
</weeklyEmail>
