<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- There must be a date and editor attribute for the weeklyEmail.
	 There also must be a teaser and an itemList which are children of the weeklyEmail.
	 Every item must have a name and category.
	 type attribute for item can be "new", "urgent", "updated" or omitted.
	 deadline attribute is for reference only.
	 date and location children of the item are optional, but info is required.
	 Items will be displayed in the order they appear, grouped by category based on the order of the categories.-->
<weeklyEmail date="March 18, 2014">
	<teaser>Official email from the UT Austin Chapter of the Society of Physics Students</teaser>
	<itemList>
		<item name="March 18" category="Message from the President">
			<info>
				Welcome back! I hope everyone had a restful spring break! Yesterday, the BICEP2 experiment
				announced the discovery of gravitational waves in the cosmic microwave background that
				prove inflation in the early universe - an
				exciting discovery for modern cosmology (more detailed description 
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.space.com/25078-universe-inflation-gravitational-waves-discovery.html"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;)! We continue to gain better understanding of how
				our magnificent universe works, but that quest is never over! So get involved in a lab, find out
				something no one knows, and present it to SPS! (Yes, that is the segue I'm using - no one reads this
				anyway) Check out the "Physics Idol" section for more info on how to do that.
				&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;~Evan Ott, SPS President
				&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="http://www.space.com/25078-universe-inflation-gravitational-waves-discovery.html"&gt;&lt;img src="http://i.space.com/images/i/000/037/671/original/b-mode-pattern-bicep2-telescope.jpg"
				width="400px"&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- SPECIAL ANNOUNCEMENTS -->
		<item name="Prospective Students Days" category="Special Announcements" type="new">
			<info>&lt;b&gt;It moved again!&lt;/b&gt; Prospective Students Days is now April 3-4 (Thursday-Friday).
				We need volunteers throughout the event (sign up &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1mfQpoDlxgziVpQHnnmurpUXXiWLYRPPk1k2Y_Sel6DI/viewform"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;). If you can help
				provide housing, please sign up
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/14D4SRERMfWi5RwQc2pV5upxhxTqa5vScf5EJCdOuQj0/viewform"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. If you signed up to help with housing, but can no longer do so, please let us know immediately.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- WEEKLY MEETINGS -->
		
		<!--CNS Activities -->

		<!-- Mentoring -->	
		<item name="Machine Shop, Electronics" category="Mentoring">
			<info>&lt;b&gt;Contact the officers if you're interested.&lt;/b&gt; Both have
				already started but if you would like to join in on the learning it may not be too late.
				Please contact us and we will see if you can be accomodated.
			</info>
		</item>

		<!-- SPS Activities -->
		<item name="Undergraduate Lecture Series: John Loftin" category="SPS Activities" type="urgent">
			<date>TODAY Tuesday, Mar. 4, 5pm</date>
			<location>CLA 0.128</location>
			<info>TODAY, John Loftin will present a talk on "A Primer on Quantum Field Theory: 
				the how and why of using field theory to do quantum mechanics in a relativistic setting."
				To get the most out of the talk, audience members should have taken Quantum 1,
				Electrodynamics, and Classical Dynamics.
			</info>
		</item>

		<item name="Cheap Lunch" category="SPS Activities">
			<location>Wednesdays, RLM Ground Floor</location>
			<info>Come grab a cheap lunch from SPS on Wednesdays! We have pizza, chips, and a 
				drink all for just $3!</info>
		</item>

		<item name="Sunday Night Study Session" category="SPS Activities">
			<date>Sundays, 6pm-???</date>
			<location>RLM 7.116</location>
			<info>It's back! Our Sunday Night Study Session (SNSS) is in full swing! For
				those who haven't been, every week we invite any and all physics majors
				and people in physics or math classes to come by to work on homework.
			With many upper-division students in attendance (and some LAs for classes),
			when you run into problems, you won't be stuck for long. We also provide
			cookies, coffee, tea, etc., to help keep you &lt;s&gt;caffeinated&lt;/s&gt;
			energized. Some come by to help or be helped! If you're interested in
			tutoring, making known that you're available during the night
			(name on a chalkboard) is a great way to earn service hours for
			Sigma Pi Sigma.</info>
		</item>
		<item name="Physics Idol (Undergrad Research Competition)" category="SPS Activities">
			<info>
				Don't forget to reserve your slot in the new Undergraduate Research
				Presentation Competition during meetings this semester! Winners will
				be judged by a combination of
				a panel and popular vote, on factors covering aspects of both the
				research itself and its presentation. Prizes will include a custom
				t-shirt and a selection of prizes, not to mention bragging rights and a nice
				bullet-point on the resume! Sign up
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://docs.google.com/a/utexas.edu/forms/d/1mtD9AHASiby4K6akdjiJTJSCxl9NJMY3hGkCyrk1RKM/viewform"&gt;
				here&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- Physics Orgs -->	
		<item name="Undergraduate Women in Physics" category="Physics Orgs">
			<info>
				UT Undergraduate Women in Physics is founded on the principle of
				promoting equality in the sciences, especially physics, both at UT and
				in the general community. We welcome all people interested in furthering
				that goal! Join their
				&lt;a target="_blank" href="https://utlists.utexas.edu/sympa/info/uwip"&gt;UTList&lt;/a&gt;
				or &lt;a target="_blank" href="https://www.facebook.com/groups/200619160136575/"&gt;Facebook group&lt;/a&gt;.
			</info>
		</item>
		<!-- CAREERS -->
		<!-- CONTACT US -->
		<item name="Comments or Questions" category="Contact Us" deadline="Never">
			<info>Have something to complain about? Or a question? Maybe an idea for a meeting or event? Or suggestions about how we use technology? Contact us at &lt;a href="mailto:spsofficers@gmail.com"&gt;spsofficers@gmail.com&lt;/a&gt; or see the links below! As always, Don't Forget To Be Awesome!</info>
		</item>
	</itemList>
</weeklyEmail>
